I learned how to run before I could walk
They silenced my voice before I could talk
Was chasin’ the highs but I still missed the mark
But you were the light, you were the light when I was lost in the dark
I told myself enough is enough
Tired of livin’ life for the rush
It’s all been a little too much
But you made me a man
Ooo
You made me a man
Take off the past
There’s no going back
Take off the mask
It ain’t gonna last
Like a mirage I thought it was magic
I told myself enough is enough
Tired of livin’ life for the rush
It’s all been a little too much
But you made me a man
Ooo
You made me a man
Take off the past
Take off the mask
Live the magic